venuelook.com 2014-09-21

# Privacy Policy | Venuelook

**Last updated on January 10, 2014**

TenX Technology Solutions ("Venuelook") is concerned about the privacy of its users (hereinafter referred to as "You" "Your" "Yourself") accessing its website www.venuelook.com ("Website") and has provided this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to familiarise You with the manner in which Venuelook collects, uses and discloses Your information collected through the Website. 

BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT PROCEED FURTHER TO USE THIS WEBSITE.

This _**Privacy Policy**_ explains how Venuelook collects personal and non-personal information, classified as mandatory or voluntary and uses, discloses and protects such information through the Website. 'Personal Information' is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person ( **"Personal Information"** ). Personal Information for the purposes of this Policy shall include, but not limited to, information regarding Your name, address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, e-mail address, etc.

You may need to provide Venuelook Your Personal Information during the course of using some services of the Venuelook, for instance, creating a User ID, provide information in Your account while registering on the Website, or provide financial information while making an online purchase, upload content, participate in any online survey or contest, communicate with Venuelook's customer service by phone, email or otherwise, provide reviews for the content available on the Website.

Venuelook collects only such Personal Information that Venuelook believes to be relevant and is required to understand You or Your interests. Venuelook collects Your Personal Information in order to record, support and facilitate Your participation in the activities You select, track Your preferences, to provide You with a customized Website experience, to notify You of any updated information and new activities and other related functions offered by Venuelook, keep You informed about latest content available on the Website, special offers, and other products and services of Venuelook, to assist You with customer service or technical support issues, to follow up with You after Your visit, to otherwise support Your relationship with Venuelook or to prevent fraud and unlawful use. 

In an effort to make our Website effective, certain information may be collected each time you visit the Website. Such information may be stored in server logs. These encrypted statistics do not identify you personally, but provide us the information regarding your visit to the Website and the type of user who is accessing our Website and certain browsing activities by You. This data may include: IP address of Your server from where the Website is being accessed, the type of browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome etc.), the operating system of Your system and the Website You last visited before visiting to our Website. The duration of Your stay on our Website is also stored in the session along with the date and time of your access. These data are used by Venuelook to understand the use and number of user visiting the Website. Some of the information related to the Website and Your visit to the Website may be shared by the sponsors, investors, advertisers, developer, strategic business partners of Venuelook and some associates in order to enhance and grow our business and the Website but we assure that these information will never include any of Your Personal Informations. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major Websites.

When You use the Website, Venuelook 's servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) may collect information indirectly and automatically about Your activities on the Website; for instance by way of cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive. This anonymous information is maintained distinctly and is not linked to the Personal Information You submit to Venuelook. 

Whether You want Your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to You. If You haven't changed Your computer's settings, most likely Your browser already accepts cookies. If You choose to decline cookies, You may not be able to fully experience all features of the Website. You can also delete Your browser cookies or disable them entirely, but this may significantly impact Your experience with the Website and may make parts of the Website non functional or inaccessible. We recommend that You leave them turned on.

We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the internet and sometimes on this Website. They may collect anonymous information about Your visits to our Website, and Your interaction with our products and services. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, address, email address, or any personally identifying information about the user.

Venuelook also uses the log file like other website servers which is the standard measures. They include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We use them to analyse trends, administer the site, track a user's movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Venuelook DOES NOT trade or sell Your Personal Information in any manner, except as specified herein, or if express consent is sought from You.

Personal Information provided by You is used only:

(a)

to facilitate Your use of the Website;

(b)

to respond to Your inquiries or fulfil Your requests for information about the various services;

(c)

to provide You with information about Venuelook's products/services and to send You information, materials, and offers from Venuelook;

(d)

to send You important information regarding the Website, changes to Venuelook's terms, conditions, and policies and/or other administrative information;

(e)

to send You surveys and marketing communications that Venuelook believes may be of interest to You;

(f)

to personalize Your experience on the Website and Venuelook's other websites by presenting advertising, products and offers tailored to You;

(g)

to help You address Your problems with the Website including addressing any technical problems;

(h)

if You purchase any content or avail of any service from the Website, to complete and fulfil Your purchase, for example, to have Your payments processed, communicate with You regarding Your purchase and provide You with related customer service; 

(i)

for proper administering of the Website;

(j)

to conduct internal reviews and data analysis for the Website (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to specific pages within the Website);

(k)

to improve the services, content and advertising on the Website;

(l)

to protect the integrity of the Website; and

(m)

to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law.

You acknowledge that apart from Your Personal Information, if You upload any content on the Website, such content may contain information including Personal Information and the same may be available to the other users of the Website. Venuelook will not be liable for the disclosure and dissemination of such Personal Information to any third parties. 

Venuelook may disclose aggregated information about the use of the Website, but it will never contain Personal Information. Venuelook does not disclose Personal Information to third parties in the normal course of operations. However, in situations when Venuelook is legally obligated to disclose information to the government or other third parties, Venuelook will do so.

Venuelook implements standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception of Personal Information. However, no internet site can fully eliminate security risks. 

2.

Shared Personal Information

You are required to submit Your information at the time of making an online purchase on the Website. Venuelook uses an online payment gateway that is operated by a third party and the information that You share with Venuelook is transferred and shared with such third party payment gateway operator. The said operator may also have access to Your online purchase history/details that You make from the Website.

Extremely sensitive information like Your credit-card details are transacted upon secure sites of approved payment gateways which are digitally under encryption, thereby providing the highest possible degree of care as per current technology. You are advised, however, that internet technology is not 100% safe and You should exercise discretion on using the same.

**Emailing Via Venuelook Account:** As part of the Services, Members and Venue Owners may communicate with each other through the use of their Accounts. Where a Member or Venue Owner has selected the option of adding one or more email addresses to an online form, the message they create in the corresponding template will be sent from Website to those email addresses on their behalf.

**Phishing:** Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to Venuelook. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your Account login information, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

**Service Providers:** We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, payment processing, web analytics and improvement of the Site's features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Service are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

**Venuelook Partners:** We may also provide Personal Information to our business partners or other trusted entities for the purpose of providing you with information on goods or services we believe will be of interest to you. You can, at any time, opt out of receiving such communications.

3.

Links to Third Party Websites

The Website and any email sent to You may also contain/display third-party advertisements and links to other websites or products and services. Venuelook does not provide any Personal Information to these third-party websites or agents or advertisers, however Venuelook reserves the right to share with You the advertisement mailers on behalf of any other parties.

Venuelook will contain links to other websites ( **"Linked Site"** ) on emails sent to You and the Website which are operated by third parties and are not controlled by, or affiliated to, or associated with, Venuelook unless expressly specified on the Website. Venuelook is not responsible for any form of transmission, whatsoever, received by You from any Linked Site. Accordingly, Venuelook does not make any representations concerning the privacy practices or policies of such third parties or terms of use of such websites, nor does Venuelook control or guarantee the accuracy, integrity, or quality of the information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, videos, messages or other materials available on such websites. The inclusion or exclusion does not imply any endorsement by Venuelook of the website, the website's provider, or the information on the website. The information provided by You to such third party websites shall be governed in accordance with the privacy policies of such websites and it is recommended that You review the privacy policy on any such websites prior to using such websites. 

These third-party websites and advertisers may use technology to send the advertisements that appear on the Website directly to Your browser. In such cases, the third party websites or advertisers automatically receive Your IP address. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize advertising content. Venuelook does not have access to or control over cookies or other features that such third party websites and advertisers may use, and the information practices of these third-party websites and advertisers are not covered by this Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. 

Venuelook strives to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of Your Personal Information and to protect Your Personal Information against unauthorized access or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. For this purpose, Venuelook adopts internal reviews of the data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where Venuelook stores Your personal data. 

Venuelook is not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive Your Personal Information. The Website also linked to many other sites and we are not/shall be not responsible for their privacy policies or practices as it is beyond our control.

Notwithstanding anything contained in this Policy or elsewhere, Venuelook shall not be held responsible for any loss, damage or misuse of Your Personal Information, if such loss, damage or misuse is attributable to a Force Majeure Event (as defined below).

A **"Force Majeure Event"** shall mean any event that is beyond the reasonable control of Venuelook and shall include, without limitation, sabotage, fire, flood, explosion, acts of God, civil commotion, strikes or industrial action of any kind, riots, insurrection, war, acts of government, computer hacking, unauthorised access to computer data and storage device, computer crashes, breach of security and encryption, etc. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@venuelook.com](mailto:info@venuelook.com)
